hedgeweb.net 2012-11-12

# Privacy Policy | Hedge Funds | Commodity Trading Advisor

**Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy applies to the Morgan Hedge web site located at www.hedgeweb.net (“Site”) and to any other VIImedia-owned web site that may be accessed through it and covers the way in which Morgan Hedge collects and uses personal information, and under which circumstances this information is disclosed to third parties. Use of this Site implies consent with the terms and conditions of this privacy policy. This policy applies to information from private individuals as well as information from companies. This privacy policy notwithstanding, Morgan Hedge reserves the right to disclose any information collected at the Site as may be requested by law . 

**1\. Information may be collected from Clients and Users of the Site in various ways.**

**Automatically collected information**

We receive and collect the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet; the Internet protocol (IP) address of the computer used; the browser software used and the operating system; the date and time of access to our site; and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to our site. We use this information to monitor the usage of our site, exclusively for internal and support purposes. 

**Information collected via cookies**

"Cookies" are small files or records that we place on your computer's hard drive to collect information about your activities on our website. The cookies transmit this information back to the computers of our website; these computers are, generally speaking, the only computers which are authorized to read such information. We only use cookies to keep track of your current right of access (after you log in). This only applies when you are not only a visitor but a registered member, that is to say, we only keep track of your right of access if you are a registered member or have ordered any of the products or services that can be accessed through the Site. Our cookies may also store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser. 

**Third party advertisers & DoubleClick DART Cookie**

Some of our advertising partners, including Google Adsense, Investing Channel, WebFinancial Group and others, may use cookies and web beacons on our Site. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this Site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to this Site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - [www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on this Site send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

This Site has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. This Site's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. You may also [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) to deactivate certain third-party cookies. 

**Information from your subscription**

When you are a registered member or subscribe to any or all of the products or services that can be accessed at the Site, or when you send a form requesting a product trial, you must provide information identifying you as customer. We use this personal customer information for internal administrative purposes, for generating statistics for marketing purposes, and for mailing information on related products. All personal information stored on our systems is secured against unauthorised access. 

**Website uses Google analytics**

This website may use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. ("Google"). Google Analytics uses "cookies", which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above. 

**2\. Use of personal customer information**

Personal customer information is used for internal administrative purposes, such as bookkeeping, and for generating statistics used by marketing and internal business administration. 

Occasionally, Morgan Hedge uses personal customer information to market products and services. We do not provide this information to third parties. 

Subcontractors We send personal customer information to third-party subcontractors and agents that work on our behalf to provide certain services. These third parties do not have the right to use the personal customer information beyond what is necessary to assist us. They are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of the personal customer information and are restricted from using such information in any way not expressly authorized by Morgan Hedge. 

**3\. Communications from the Site**

You may receive the following communications through this Site: 

  * Emails related to your membership or the purchase of our services.
  * Communications containing information about any of the sites referred to under the term Site, or about Morgan Hedge and its partners, products and services.
  * Relevant emails and information if you choose to subscribe to any of the available services offered at the Site (if applicable).

**4\. Correcting and removing your personal information**

For corrections to personal customer information, or for having personal customer information removed from our systems, please send us an email. Please note that it is not possible to have personal customer information removed as long as you are subscribing to any of the products or services accessible through the Site due to the administrative necessity of keeping customer contact information. In order to have personal customer information removed, you must first consent to terminate the subscription. 

**5\. Linking to third-party web sites**

When you click on links and banners on our site that take you to third-party web sites, you will be subject to the third parties' privacy policies. While we support the protection of privacy on the Internet, Morgan Hedge cannot be responsible for the actions of any third-party web sites. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement of any and every site you visit, whether you are linking from our site or browsing on your own. 

**6\. Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

**7\. Changes to Privacy Policy**

This privacy policy was last amended on March 16, 2009. Morgan Hedge reserves the right to modify or amend this policy at any time by posting the revised privacy policy on the Site. The changes will only affect the information we collect after the effective date of the change to our privacy policy, unless we clearly express otherwise.
